Guide to the Joseph R. Lentol papers CBHM.0004
Center for Brooklyn History
Joseph R. Lentol Papers
1951-2020
Center for Brooklyn History
Radezky, Eric
Lentol, Joseph R., 1943-
Lentol, Edward S., 1909-1981
CBHM.0004
6.92 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize boxes, and 4 flat file folders.
The Joseph R. Lentol papers, 1951-2020, includes correspondence, press releases, photographs, flyers, posters, and news clippings related to Lentol's career as New York State Assemblyman for Kings County District 50 and his father Edward S. Lentol's career as a New York State Assemblyman and Senator. The collection also includes campaign flyers collected from New York City and State elections from 2001 to 2020.
Scope and Contents
The Joseph R. Lentol papers, 1951-2020, includes correspondence, press releases, campaign promotional material, photographs, and news clippings from Joseph R. Lentol's career as a New York State Assemblyman for Kings County Assembly District (AD) 58 from 1973-1982 and AD 50 1983-2020, covering the neighborhoods of Greenpoint, Williamsburg, and Fort Greene (Fort Greene was covered after 1980 census reapportionment). These files from Lentol's office reflect constituent complaints and requests, projects Lentol worked on, and organizations with which he was involved.
This collection also includes promotional flyers collected from various New York City and State political campaigns between 2001 and 2020. There are also papers from the career of Edward S. Lentol who was Joseph R. Lentol's father and served as New York State Assemblyman, Senator, and Supreme Court justice. The Edward S. Lentol papers do not cover the time he served as New York State Supreme Court justice and most of those materials are election results printed in newspapers, a 1958 Democratic Campaign Handbook, photographs, and promotional campaign materials.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Eric Radezky, 2021.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series:
Series 1: New York State Assembly office files, circa 1963 - 2020
Series 2: Other political campaign flyers, 2001-2020
Series 3: Edward S. Lentol papers, 1951-1966
Biographical note
Joseph R. Lentol was born on January 15, 1943. His mother was Matilda A. Postis and his father was New York State Assemblyman, Senator, and Supreme Court justice Edward S. Lentol. Before running for office, Lentol was Assistant District Attorney in Kings County.
Lentol was first elected to the New York State Assembly for Assembly District (AD) 58 in 1972, running for an open seat after Assemblyman Chester Straub left to run for New York State Senator. He ran against Republican Vinny Abate in the 1972 and 1974 elections. In 1978, Roman Popadiuk ran against Lentol in the Democratic primary and Lentol won. Nick Stefanizzi, head of the local school board, ran campaigns against Lentol in the Democratic primaries in 1980 and 1982. These were close elections, but Lentol won both primaries. The 58th AD was redistricted and assigned a new number, AD 50, after the 1980 census. Fort Greene was added to this Assembly District in 1982.
Between 1983 and 2010, Lentol did not have any Democratic primary challengers. André Soleil, a lawyer, ran against Lentol in the 2010 Democratic primary. About 6,000 votes were cast in the 2010 primary and Lentol won by a wide margin. Lentol lost to Democrat Emily Gallagher in the 2020 election. There was a large voter turnout for the 2020 election, around 20,000 people.
During his time as a New York State Assemblyman, Lentol was the Chair of the Assembly's Committee on Codes (1992-2020), the Committee on Governmental Employees, the Committee on Governmental Operations, and the Administrative Regulations Review Commission. Lentol was also Dean of the Brooklyn Delegation of the Assembly from 2001 to 2020, coordinating efforts that called on all Brooklyn Assemblymembers to work together on projects with borough-wide implications.
Lentol advocated for waterfront and green space preservation, criminal justice reform, and affordable housing. In 2000, Lentol was selected to be a part of the Election Modernization Task Force, which made recommendations to the State on how to increase voter registration and turnout.
Lentol was a part of the New York Conference of Italian-American Legislators and the New York State Legislative Pilots Association.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Related Materials
Center for Brooklyn History holds the following related materials:
- The Greenpoint Environmental History Project is available on Center for Brooklyn History's digital collections.
- The Brooklyn Daily Eagle photographs (BCMS.0002) has photographs of Edward S. Lentol
- Greenpoint Petroleum Remediation Project (GPRP) records, 1995-2015 (BCMS.0062)
- Seneca Club of Kings County records, 1928-2015 (2016.042)
The New York State Library holds volumes of hearings from the New York State Legislature Assembly Standing Committee on Codes.
Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)--Politics and government; New York (State) |x Politics and government; Greenpoint (New York, N.Y.); Williamsburg (New York, N.Y.); Fort Greene (New York, N.Y.); Oil spills--Cleanup; Newtown Creek (Kings County-New York County, N.Y.); Congestion pricing; Correspondence; Press releases; Photographs; Flyers (printed matter); Political posters; Political campaigns -- New York (State) -- New York; Capital punishment; Radezky, Eric; New York (State). Legislature. Assembly; Lentol, Edward S., 1909-1981; Lentol, Joseph R., 1943-; New York Conference of Italian-American Legislators
- Series 1: New York State Assembly office files, circa 1963 - 2020
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1: New York State Assembly office files, circa 1963-2020, includes correspondence, press releases, memoranda, photographs, flyers, posters, and news clippings related to Joseph R. Lentol's career as New York State Assemblyman and his office's activities representing District 50, covering the north Brooklyn neighborhoods of Greenpoint, Williamsburg, and Fort Greene. Much of the correspondence is Lentol writing to city agencies regarding constituent requests and complaints.
  Sub-series 1.2: Eric Radezky files is separate from Sub-series 1.1: Joseph R. Lentol files because the Eric Radezky files cover projects that Radezky was personally involved in while an employee from 2006 to 2020. There may be some duplicates of correspondence in the sub-series within that time period.
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged in two sub-series:
  Sub-series 1.1: Joseph R. Lentol files, circa 1963 - 2020
  Sub-series 1.2: Eric Radezky files, 2004-2020
  - Sub-series 1.1: Joseph R. Lentol files, circa 1963 - 2020
    Sub-series 1.1: Joseph R. Lentol files, circa 1963-2020, includes correspondence, photographs, press releases, posters, flyers, a VHS tape, and news clippings related to Joseph R. Lentol's career as a New York State Assemblyman.
    The Greenpoint oil spill documents include correspondence and informational documents about efforts to clean up Newtown Creek between 2006 and 2016. Consent orders from lawsuits against Chevron and BP are also included.
    Congestion pricing documents include correspondence and informational documents regarding congestion pricing as a strategy for reducing traffic congestion during peak hours.
    Photographs depict Lentol with different constituent groups, politicians, and celebrities, and at events and bill signings.
    Also included in this sub-series is Joseph R. Lentol's "Albany bag," a leather briefcase used by Lentol for over 40 years and up until his last visit in 2020.
    The sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    - [Brooklyn Public Library card], circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - [Photograph of Boxing Greats of Philadelphia], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - [Newspaper election results], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [Election endorsements], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - [Citizens Union Voters Directory], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [Board of Elections 58th Assembly District map], 1973 (Folder Flat File 4 of 4)
    - Photos of Joe Lentol and other elected officials, circa 1963 - 2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - [New York State Assemblyman re-election campaign flyers], 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7, Box 9, Folder 3)
    - [Assemblyman Lentol newsletter], 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - [Re-election campaign posters], 1974 (Folder Flat File 1 of 4)
    - [New York State] Assembly ID cards, 1974-2020 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - [Photograph of Joseph R. Lentol as Acting Speaker], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - [Green Oaks Club portrait], circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - [Photograph of Joseph R. Lentol with taxi driver], circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - [Photograph of Assemblymembers and Councilmembers], circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - [St. Stan's - Brooklyn, New York State Capitol visit photograph], circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - [Photograph with Winthrope Civic Association], circa 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - [Re-election campaign poster versus Roman Papadiuk], 1978 (Folder Flat File 2 of 4)
    - [Public hearing on reopening of People's Firehouse in Williamsburg photograph], circa 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - [New York Transit Police swearing in ceremony], circa 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - [Photograph of Officers of Badame Sessa Memorial Post 1336], circa 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - [Photographs of Grand Street Park], 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - [Greenpoint Gazette articles], 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Photos of Lentol with various constituent groups, 1979-2014 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Groups and individuals depicted in these photographs include: Laurie Szalyga, Irene Klementovic, Colin Powell, Sal Albanese, Tenants' Labor Day, Tish Cianciotta, Andrea Torre, Vinny Spinola, Martha Holstein, United Federation of Teachers, and Father Peter Young, among others.
    - Various headshots and photos of AM Joe Lentol through the years, 1980-2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - [Greenpoint Lions Installation and Testimonial Dinner photograph], circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - [Photographs of Joseph R. Lentol with Edward Koch], circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - [Photograph of Joseph R. Lentol with Fred Richmond], circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - [Abraham and Straus store card], circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - [New York State Assemblyman re-election campaign flyers], 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - [Re-election campaign poster], 1980 (Folder Flat File 3 of 4)
    - [Italian-American Legislators, New York Conference photograph], 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - [Dinner honoring Senator Al D'Amato photograph], 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - [Rules Committee Dinner photograph], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - [Seneca Club Dinner photograph], 1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - [Photograph of Joseph R. Lentol and Mario Cuomo], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Photos with recognizable elected officials and celebrities, 1984-2016 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Individuals depicted in these photographs include: Cardinal Timothy Dolan, Mike Tyson, Kevin Rooney, Nick Perry, Sheldon Silver, Joe Crowley, Linda Minucci, Denny Farrell, Joe Robach, Richard Kind, Chazz Palminteri, Joe Pantoliano, Mike Bloomberg, Mel Brooks, Letitia "Tish" James, George Pataki, and Mickey Mouse.
    - [Photograph of Ridgewood-Bushwick Senior Citizens Council Conference], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - [New York State Assembly softball team photograph], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - [Model Block Awards Breakfast], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - [Photograph with Nick Spano], circa 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - [Congratulatory letter from Governor Mario Cuomo to Lentol], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - [Pilots Dinner photograph], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - [Criminal justice bill signing photograph], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - [Citibank Citigrants check presentation to Greenpoint Volunteer Ambulance Corps (GVAC)], 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - [Photographs with Al Gore], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - [Photographs of PSC (Public Service Commission [?]) ribbon cutting], circa 1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Assemblyman Lentol office documents and correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Assemblyman Lentol office documents and correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - [Pilots Dinner photograph], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - [Photograph of Con Edison, 179 Green Street], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - [Good Joe's Days and Brooklyn and Albany staff photographs], circa 1990-2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - [Photographs with El Puente Toxic Avengers], circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - [New York State Police Lateral Transfer Bill photograph], circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - [Photograph of bill signing with Mario Cuomo and David Dinkins], circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - [Photograph with Mario Cuomo], circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - [New York Law Journal article "Revised 'Son-of-Sam' Law Signed by Governor Cuomo"], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - [Photograph of Lentol Garden bill signing], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Officer Steven McDonald Little League ceremony [photographs], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - [Lentol Garden dedication ceremony program], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - [Pilots Dinner photograph], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - [Photograph with Moshe Teitelbaum], circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Proposal from Democratic Reform Caucus led by Assemblyman Bragman, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Documents from attempted NYSA [New York State Assembly] coup of Speaker Sheldon Silver, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - [Clinton-Washington Avenue G line mural], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [Photographs with Hilary Clinton], circa 2001-2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Assemblyman Lentol press releases, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - [Block Magazine, Joseph R. Lentol profile], 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - [Greenpoint Gazette election ad and articles], 2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Assemblyman Lentol press releases, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Photos of various Italian-American days and Greek-American days in Albany, 2003-2019 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Press releases, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - [National Conference of State Legislatures Media Interview Guide], 2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Williamsburg rezoning meeting documents, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - [Crossfire with Lentol on death penalty opinion], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      This VHS tape is undigitized and not available for research use.
      VHS; Runtime: unknown
      Existence and Location of Copies
      A transcript of this episode is available online on CNN.com.
    - Press releases, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - [Greenpoint Little League photographs], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [Bill in support of Child Victims Act press conference photograph], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - [Death penalty and budget hearing photographs], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Press releases, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Greenpoint oil spill consent decrees, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Greenpoint oil spill consent decrees, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Greenpoint oil spill consent decrees, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Greenpoint oil spill consent decrees, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn College commencement [photograph], 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      The DVD "Contested Streets: Breaking New York City Gridlock" is not available for research use.
      DVD; Runtime: 57 minutes
      This content is available to view on Vimeo from StreetFilms.
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Greenpoint oil spill documents, 2006-2010 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - [New York State Assembly Pilots], 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Greenpoint oil spill documents, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Press releases, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - [Opening of new Brooklyn Children's Museum photograph], 2008 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Congestion pricing documents, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - [Constituent contact], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - [Correspondence], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - [Met Council photograph], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Blessing of the Animals, St. Cecilia's [photographs], circa 2010 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Dedication of BARC Avenue co-naming [photograph], circa 2010 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - [2010 State Assembly Primary campaign materials] (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - [9/11 Memorial construction site photographs], 2011 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - [Photograph with Robert Duffy and Andrew Kimball], 2012 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - [Marie Sadowski plaque dedication, McGolrick Park photographs], 2012 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - [North Brooklyn Development Corporation ribbon cutting photographs], 2013 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Greenpoint oil spill documents, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - [Seneca Club Dinner photograph], 2017 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - [Photographs with Andrew Cuomo], 2017 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - [Photograph of Joseph R. Lentol and Denny Farrell], 2017 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - [Volunteer thank you letters], 2018 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - [Assemblyman Lentol newsletters], 2019-2020 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - [Designating petition training materials], 2020 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - [New York State Assemblyman election campaign poster], 2020 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - [Designating petition training materials], 2020 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - [2020 Assemblyman campaign flyers] (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - [Greenpoint Gazette Eric Radezky op-ed], 2020 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - [The LOOM issues], 2020 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Joseph R. Lentol biography, 2020 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Items from last trip to Albany in March 2020 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
    - [Joseph R. Lentol's briefcase], circa 1970 (Box 10)
  - Sub-series 1.2: Eric Radezky files, 2004-2020
    Biographical Note
    Eric Radezky worked for Assemblyman Joseph R. Lentol from 2006 to 2020 and was District Office Director from 2013 to 2020. As District Office Director, Radezky oversaw office management, staff development, and project management.
    Radezky has a Ph.D. in Political Science from Rutgers University, an M.A. in Urban Planning and Public Policy from Brooklyn College, and a B.S. in Communications from Boston University. As of 2023, he is Director of Governmental and External Affairs at Hostos Community College and teaches classes as an adjunct professor at LaGuardia Community College.
    Sub-series 1.2: Eric Radezky files, 2004-2020, consists of files related to issues and cases Eric Radezky was personally involved in while working for Assemblyman Lentol. This includes press releases, letters to and from constituents, and "scanned case files," which are groups of files related to a certain issue, agency, or business over a period of years, such as alternate side parking, Department of Transportation, and the Pod Hotel on Metropolitan Avenue.
    Many of the files are not on official letterhead because they were printed out on Assemblyman Lentol's letterhead and sent out in physical mailings.
    This sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    - [Eric Radezky's files USB drive], 2004-2020 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      This USB drive is not available for research use. Access to physical copies of these files are available on-site in the Othmer Library at Center for Brooklyn History.
    - Scanned case files - letters of support, 2004-2017 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Letters, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Letters, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Press releases, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Letters, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Press releases, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Scanned case files - DOT [Department of Transportation], 2007-2014 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Letters, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Press releases, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Scanned case files - MTA issues, 2008-2019 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Scanned case files - Parks issues, 2008-2019 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Letters, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Press releases, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Scanned case files - ASP [Alternate side parking] letters, 2009-2017 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Letters, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Press releases, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Letters, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Press releases, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Letters, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Press releases, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Scanned case files - Pulaski bike lane, 2012-2014 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Scanned case files - DSNY [The City of New York Department of Sanitation] Scorecard, 2012-2018 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Letters, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Press releases, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Scanned case files - MTA L line shutdown letter, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Scanned case files - film and TV letters, 2013-2016 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Letters, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Press releases, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Letters, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Scanned case files - DOT [Department of Transportation], 2015-2018 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Scanned case files - NYCHA, Enviro, GP [Greepoint] school, codes, 2015-2019 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Letters, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Press releases, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Scanned case files - Fillmore Place - POD Hotel, 2016-2017 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Scanned case files - MTA 40 Quay, 2016-2019 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Press releases, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Scanned case files - DEP [Department of Environmental Protection] long-term control plan, 2017-2020 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Letters, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Press releases, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Scanned case files - NYCHA RAD-PACT [New York City Housing Authority Rental Assistance Demonstration - Permanent Affordability Commitment Together]letters, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Letters, 2019 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Press releases, 2019 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Scanned case files - DOT [Department of Transportation], 2019-2020 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Scanned case files - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] Newtown Creek superfund site, 2019 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Letters, 2020 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Press releases, 2020 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series 2: Other political campaign flyers, 2001-2020
  Series 2: Other political campaign flyers, 2001-2020, includes campaign flyers Lentol collected from other New York City and State political campaigns. Most of the politicians were active in Brooklyn with some citywide and statewide races represented; a few flyers relate to races in Sand Lake, New York, a town near Albany, New York. Some flyers are also from political action groups, such as the Lambda Independent Democrats of Brooklyn.
  The series is in alphabetical order.
  - [1199 SEIU Political Action Fund], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - [Richard Aborn], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - [Isaac Abraham], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - [Maria Aragona], 2020 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - [Ken Baer], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - [Herb Berman], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - [Doug Biviano], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - [Mike Bloomberg], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 17)